[
    {
        "question": "Who was not part of the original X-Men?",
        "choice1": "Storm",
        "choice2": "Cyclops",
        "choice3": "Iceman",
        "choice4": "Beast",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Where does Dr. Strange seek out a cure for his damaged hands?",
        "choice1": "China",
        "choice2": "Tibet",
        "choice3": "Mongolia",
        "choice4": "New York",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "How old is thor",
        "choice1": "100",
        "choice2": "500",
        "choice3": "1000",
        "choice4": "1500",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Where do the X-men train?",
        "choice1": "Threat Room",
        "choice2": "Menace Room",
        "choice3": "Crisis Room",
        "choice4": "Danger Room",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "The comic book version of 'Iron Man' is based on what real-life eccentric?",
        "choice1": "Warren Beatty",
        "choice2": "Elon Musk",
        "choice3": "Howard Hughes",
        "choice4": "Stan Lee",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Vanessa Marianna becomes the wife of this Marvel supervillain",
        "choice1": "Dr. Octopus",
        "choice2": "Kingpin",
        "choice3": "Magneto",
        "choice4": "Dr. Doom",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which super hero is known as the man without fear?",
        "choice1": "Moon Knight",
        "choice2": "Bullseye",
        "choice3": "Wolverine",
        "choice4": "Daredevil",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Which member of the X-men has a pet dragon?",
        "choice1": "Phoenix",
        "choice2": "Shadowcat",
        "choice3": "Wolverine",
        "choice4": "Nightcrawler",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Victor von Doom's alter ego?",
        "choice1": "Dr. Manhattan",
        "choice2": "Dr. Fate",
        "choice3": "Dr. Doom",
        "choice4": "Dr. Strange",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the first marvel character to appear in a comic book?",
        "choice1": "Sub-Mariner",
        "choice2": "Spider-Man",
        "choice3": "Captain America",
        "choice4": "Human Torch",
        "answer": 1
    }
]